Evil doesn't knock... It has the key!
The Landlady is a horror, thriller film directed by Robert Malenfant.
Melanie decides that one of her tenants would be perfect as her husband and
decides to eliminate everyone who might interfere in her plans.
Melanie Leroy, played by Talia Shire.
Patrick Forman, played by Jack Coleman.
Pepper McAllen, played by Bruce Weitz.
Liz Reese, played by Melissa Behr.
Justine Welch, played by Bette Ford.
Jenny Hagen, played by Dee Freeman.
The Notorious Landlady is a 1962 American comedy mystery film
starring Kim Novak, Jack Lemmon, and Fred Astaire.
The film was directed by Richard Quine, with a script by Blake Edwards and Larry
Gelbart based on the short story "The Notorious Tenant" by Margery Sharp.
The tone is dark and intense.